Guide to the John Simpson Papers, 1825-1875 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Poetry, Plays, and Amusements Series, 1848 Sept. 16-1855 Nov. 13 and undated, (2 folders)
  - Oversize broadsides, 1848, (2 items) (Box 6)
    Fliers advertising a play on the Plover and a dance, hosted on the ship, to which the local Inuit were apparently invited.